

MA-336, College Ring 6, Bremen, 28759, Germany

□ (+49) 1511-5661770 | ■ theparthshukla@gmail.com | 💣 www.parthshukla.dev | 🖸 theparthshukla | 🛅 theparthshukla

"Do, or do not. There is no try."

Summary_

Creative and engaged first year Computer Science student with experience in design and web development. Interested in using my passion for problem solving to build better solutions for challenging tasks and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Education

Jacobs University

Bremen, Germany

Aug. 2019 - Present

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Work Experience _____

UWC Mahindra College

Pune,India

Mar. 2018 - Jan. 2019

SECRETARY OF THE COLLEGE ASSEMBLY

- · Facilitated, supported, and coordinated all activities of the student council.
- Developed, promoted, and conducted a variety of extra curricular programs for students.
- · Organized and coordinated various fundraising programs and funfair events to generate revenue.
- Planned, arranged, and chaired all meetings with council members, as needed.

Leave No Fingerprints

Mumbai.India

WEB DEVELOPER AND GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Mar. 2017 - June. 2019

- Developed and maintained the front end functionality of websites.
- Devised SEO strategies based around specific keywords.

Ahmedabad Student Parliament

Ahmedabad,India

Duna India

HEAD OF IT AND LOGISTICS

Jun. 2017 - May. 2018

- · Arranged and coordinated all on-site logistics, including transportation, accommodations, meals, guest speakers and audiovisual support.
- Appointed and led a highly skilled IT team to create event infrastructure as well as provide support during the length of the events.

Honors & Awards

Dunnay IIn TCCITW:

2010	Runner Op, 1.C.3 II WIZ	Fulle, illulu
2017	1st Place , Reliance Foundation JrNBA Competition	Mumbai,India
2017	Da Vinci Scholar, World Scholar's Cup	Delhi, India
2017	1st Place , CISCE National Debate Final	Kolkata,India
2017	Student of The Year, Anand Niketan School	Ahmedabad, India
2016	Student of The Year, Anand Niketan School	Ahmedabad, India

Skills_

2010

Programming Experienced: JAVA, Python Basic:C, C++,

Tools Experienced:Git

Front-end Experienced: HTML5 Basic: REACT

Languages Native: English, Hindi Basic: Spanish, German

Extracurricular Activity ___

Computers for All

Pune, India

SERVICE PROGRAM CO-ORDINATOR

Aug. 2017 - Jan. 2019

• Set up a functional computer lab and gave basic computer education to people of all age groups in the village of Asade.